surplusammo.com 2018-05-11

# Privacy Policy | Surplusammo.com

**_Surplusammo.com privacy policy_**

We are committed to protecting your privacy and want you to know what type of information we collect and what we do with it. If you have questions, comments, or concerns regarding our privacy policy please contact us at:

suggestions@surplusammo.com

**What information we collect & use:**

**Account Sign-Up and Ordering**

We collect and retain the following information when you create an account to place an order with us:

  * Name
  * Billing address
  * Shipping address
  * Email address
  * Phone numbers 

We use this information to process your order.  Your information will not be shared with anyone.

If you do not want to us to retain your information in our system for future order processing, call or write us and we will remove your information.  Please note that information used for prior order history and communication will be retained for our company archival purposes only.

**Cookies**

To place an order on our site, your browser must have cookies turned on. A cookie allows us to recognize you the next time you fill out an order on our site. To prevent your personal information from being read by other web sites, our cookie is a unique, encrypted string that contains no personal information. You may purge our cookie from your computer’s browser at any time. However, you will have to receive a new cookie if you wish to place an order through our web site.

**Email Newsletter Registration**

If you register to receive our newsletter or place an order with us, we collect and retain the following:

  * Name
  * Email Address
  * Mailing Address
  * Phone Number

We do not share your name and email address with anyone. If you do not want to receive our email newsletter you may opt out by clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the newsletter e-mail once received or by contacting us directly and we can unsubscribe you manually.

**Third Parties**

We use third parties to provide a variety of services and give them the following information:

  * Credit card processing company (e-commerce tied to our website): Name, billing address, and credit card number and expiration date.
  * Shipping company (UPS, USPS, other): Name, shipping address, phone number, package weight and order number(s).
  * List Services (aforementioned newsletter): Name, email and shipping address.
  * Analytics Services (website analytics): Age, gender, first-party cookies & interests.   
(opt out of google analytics here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout))

**ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

**Links**

Our website, email communications and promotions may contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the content of these sites or their privacy policies. It is your responsibility to determine what those privacy policies are and what information is being collected.

**_Legal Disclaimer_**

Although we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may be required to disclose personal information when required by law if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or a legal process served on Surplusammo.com.
